Astrid Gamoneda



astrid.gamoneda@gmail.com



https://www.astrid.cf/



https://www.linkedin.com/in/as

Software Engineer

Experience

Backend Engineer

Empathy.co

2020-Current

- API design, writing, maintenance and on-call support.
- Creating reusable code and libraries.
- Developing projects focusing on privacy and decentralization.
- Collaborating with UX/UI designers and front-end developers.
- Deploying services using Kubernetes and Cloudfront.
- Scrum
- Presenting in the MyData2022 conference in Helsinki.

Computer Science Intern

WESO (Web Semantic Oviedo)

2019 - 2020

- Elaborated a proof-of-concept application for the decentralization of e-commerce search.
- Quickly learned state of the art technologies and applied to solve problems

Web Developer Summer Intern

Cotera.es

2019 - 2019

- A 3 month internship in the local web design company
 coters as
- Developed user interfaces with modern JavaScript frameworks,
 HTML5 and CSS3.

Professional Summary

Bringing more than 2 years of experience collaborating to the design, build, documentation, deployment, maintenance and bringing code to production in transversal backend projects. Focused on creating clean, robust code and with a growth mindset constantly looking towards improvement.

Education

International University Valencia

Master in Artificial Intelligence

2022 - Expected 2023

Remotely balancing attending a masters with remote work

Oviedo University

Bachelor in Software Engineer

2016 - 2020

University of South Florida

Exchange Program

2018

Skills

- Programming Languages: Java, C#, Python, Javascript,
 Typescript, HTML, CSS, C, C++, Ruby.
- Tools: ElasticSearch, Jenkins, Maven, LINQ, Travis, rdf, Sql, MongoDB, MatLab.
- DevOps Engineering: Docker, Kubernetes, GCP, AWS
- Frameworks: Node, Django, Springboot, Spring, Angular.js, React.js,
- Version Control Systems: Git, GitHub
- Continuous Improvement
- Best Practices and Methodologies

Astrid Gamoneda

 \bigvee

astrid.gamoneda@gmail.com



https://www.astrid.cf/



https://www.linkedin.com/in/as

Ingeniera de Software

Experiencia

Ingeniera Backend

Empathy.co

2020-Actualidad

- Diseño, elaboración, mantenimiento y apoyo en guardias de
- Creación de códifo reusable y librerías.
- Desarrollo de proyectos enfocados hacia la privacidad y la descentralización.
- Colaboración con diseñadores UX y desarrolladores front-end.
- Desplegando servicios usando Kubernetes and Cloudfront.
- Scrum
- Participación en la conferencia MyData2022 en Helsinki.

Prácticas de Investigación

WESO (Web Semantic Oviedo)

2019 - 2020

- Elaboración de una aplicación proof-of-concept para la descentrazación de la búsqueda del e-commerce.
- Rápido aprendizaje de tecnologías de vanguardia para resolver problemas.

Prácticas de desarrollo web

Cotera.es

2019 - 2019

- Unas prácticas de 3 meses en la empresa local cotera.es.
- Desarrollo de interfaces de usuario usando Wordpress, JavaScript, HTML5 and CSS3.

Resumen Profesional

Aportando más de 2 años de experiencia colaborando en el diseño, construcción, documentación, despliegue, mantenimiento y puesta en producción de código en proyectos transversales de backend. Centrado en la creación de código limpio y robusto con una mentalidad de crecimiento que busca constantemente la mejora.

Education

International University Valencia

Master in Artificial Intelligence

2022 - Previsto 2023

Cursando un máster compaginando con el trabajo a distancia

Oviedo University

Bachelor in Software Engineer

2016 - 2020

University of South Florida

Exchange Program

2018

Aptitudes

- Lenguajes de programación: Java, C#, Python, Javascript,
 Typescript, HTML, CSS, C, C++, Ruby.
- Herramientas: ElasticSearch, Jenkins, Maven, LINQ, Travis, rdf, Sql, MongoDB, MatLab.
- DevOps: Docker, Kubernetes, GCP, AWS
- Marcos de trabajo: Node, Django, Springboot, Spring,
 Angular.js, React.js,
- Control de versiones: Git, GitHub
- Mejores Prácticas y metodologías.